

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT WITH ONE YEAR OF EXI

wu.kevin.2520@gmail.com | In KevinIsMyName | In Ke

Summary ____

Kevin is a pre-junior (year 3/5) studying computer science at Drexel University. He has one year of experience in full stack development. He is excited to learn more about technologies and its subfields and he is a go-getter that enjoys problem solving and socializing with others.

Education

Drexel University Philadelphia, PA

Sep. 2018 – June 2023 **B.S. AND M.S. COMPUTER SCIENCE**

GPA: 3.52 / 4.00

Skills

Languages Python · TypeScript · Java

Technologies | React.js · SQL · MS Azure · Docker

Tools VS Code · IntelliJ · GitHub · Unix

Experience _____

Bentley Systems Philadelphia, PA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER CO-OP Mar. 2021 - Present

- Automated tests of npm test packages to minimize test flakiness via MS Azure CI/CD caching
- · Created a responsive dashboard for visualizing our global services and their respective statuses via React.js & Azure Functions
- · Aggregated and visualized data & metrics for the team's quarterly reports via PowerBI

Susquehanna International Group, LLP

Bala Cynwyd, PA

Apr. 2020 - Sep. 2020 SOFTWARE ENGINEER CO-OP

- Developed a Python Flask web app for team leads to manage 30 trader-lead hierarchies consistently, saving DBAs hours of labor
- Developed a file listener as a fail-safe method to extract over 30 types of market data to databases via Python
- Improved file parsing and RAM performance with buffers & raw byte reading for opening files larger than 5 gigabytes
- Spearheaded 2 projects and collaborated with 7 members across 2 teams to effectively develop and quickly deploy software

Projects _____

Nov. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- Developed a containerized web app that simulates a proof-of-work blockchain
- Created fast responsive web UI in Vue.js for generating new and regenerating block data

Apr. 2019

- Developed a web app that scans receipts via Tesseract OCR and visualizes purchase taxonomy by classifying purchases via NLP API
- Created frontend to handle Tesseract OCR responses from user-provided receipts

Extracurriculars ___

Drexel University College of Computing & Informatics (CCI)

Philadelphia, PA

DEAN'S AMBASSADOR

MARKETING DIRECTOR

Sep. 2019 - Present

· Promoting CCI to and meeting with new students through recruiting events such as Open House

Society of Asian Scientists and Engineers - Drexel Chapter

Philadelphia, PA Aug. 2020 - July 2021

- Created 7-10 event graphics per quarter via Canva and Photoshop, and advertising through Facebook and Instagram
- Outreached to new students of College of Engineering and College of Computing & Informatics